Hello and welcome to the permanent data storage section.
I know that's a little bit of a media title.
Their data storage section it sounds a little bit more intense than it is.
The basic idea here is we've been building some awesome apps for example that favorite locations out
but we haven't been able to save any information as soon as we close the app bring a back up it's like
we're here for the very first time and that's not ideal for most of the apps that we're going to build.
So in this section you're going to learn how do you store and save information we're going to learn
how to do some of it in a little bit of a local easy to use situation.
But also we're going to learn how to work with a full blown QOL database now don't worry if you don't
know that is maybe you've heard about it before but you're going to learn a little bit about the programming
language called.
Q Well I guess it's not technically a programming language but we'll dive into that too.
But go ahead and enjoy permanent data storage.